finapp.co.in 2019-04-15

# Privacy Policy - FinApp

At FinApp, we value our Site Visitors and Store Members, and respect your right to privacy.  
We do not engage in SPAM, nor do we share the personal contact information  
of our stores, visitors, or their friends, relatives, and associates with  
third parties. The following information provides more detail about our  
Privacy Policy.

**Use and Collection of Store and Site Visitor Information**

The only personal information collected by FinApp is submitted  
voluntarily by Site Visitors through email correspondence. Other information  
collected by FinApp includes site usage statistics and click-through  
information, which is collected electronically as a result of actions taken  
by Site Visitors. FinApp personnel are fully educated about the  
policies and practices of FinApp in regards to protecting voluntarily  
submitted personal information from outside access, and take every measure  
possible to prevent unauthorized use or disclosure. 

Since FinApp is only a guide service for Site Visitors using the  
Internet to research and locate products and services, we do not engage  
in customer-to-store transactions, and therefore do not collect or use personal  
credit card information from Site Visitors. 

Any other personally identifiable information, including names, addresses,  
telephone numbers and email addresses, received by FinApp from  
Site Visitors is exclusively and voluntarily submitted on the part of the  
visitor via email. Personally identifiable information provided in such  
correspondence is not stored at our website, is only used for responding  
to the respective query, and is otherwise not used for marketing promotions,  
SPAM or any other purpose. Site Visitors who do not want their personally  
identifiable information made available to FinApp should not submit  
such information. 

**  
Site Usage, Searches and Click-Throughs**  
Statistics about site usage, searches and click-throughs gathered by FinApp  
are collected in an aggregate format only. This information is used to assess  
traffic to the website, and to report search and click-through information  
to individual Store Members. 

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log  
files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol)  
address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable),  
the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox),  
the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our  
site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences  
when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once  
in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as  
forums.

We also use third party advertisements  
on FinApp to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use  
technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site,  
which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google  
AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser  
you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  
This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real  
estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based  
on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents  
cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or  
selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser  
settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet  
Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our  
site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login  
to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Google, as a third-party vendor,  
uses cookies to serve ads on your site. * Google’s use of the DART cookie  
enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites  
and other sites on the Internet. * Users may opt out of the use of the DART  
cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**Protection of Site Visitor  
Information **  
Once received by FinApp, email submitted voluntarily by Site Visitors  
is kept absolutely confidential. Access to this information is restricted  
to FinApp administrators, and personally identifiable information  
contained in the email is only used to respond to the respective query.  
FinApp does not rent, sell or exchange the email addresses of Site  
Visitors, or of their friends, associates or relatives, to any third party,  
including its store members. In addition, FinApp does not use these  
email addresses to engage in SPAM activities. Email voluntarily submitted  
by Site Visitors is removed from our records following its review.

FinApp gives Store Members information about aggregate searches  
and click-throughs on their products only. FinApp does not report  
the data of one store to any other store. 

Aggregate statistics about general site usage is collected anonymously.  
Site Visitors are not personally tracked in any way. 

**Notification of Privacy Policies**  
This policy statement informs FinApp Site Visitors that FinApp  
will keep their personally identifiable information confidential.

**Opt-Out / Removal of Information**  
Since FinApp does not solicit personally identifiable information  
from site visitors, we do not have an opt-out policy. 

**Use of Site by Minors**  
FinApp does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information  
from children under the age of 13. 

FinApp further does not promote, condone or endorse the dissemination  
of information, or sale of products and services to minors when prohibited  
by law; including the dissemination or sale of pornographic materials to  
minors; and the sale of firearms, tobacco and alcohol to minors.

**Site Visitor Interaction with Stores**  
The FinApp website includes links to third-party websites. FinApp  
has no control over the privacy practices of these websites, or of our member  
Stores. Once a Site Visitor has linked from FinApp to a third-party  
website, the visitor is responsible for obtaining Privacy Policy information  
from the third-party site. 

**Accessing Personal Information**  
Since FinApp does not collect personally identifiable information  
from Site Visitors, access is not provided. 

If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy for FinApp,  
please contact us at mail@finapp.in
